{"id_nergrit_ner": {"description": "Nergrit Corpus is a dataset collection for Indonesian Named Entity Recognition, Statement Extraction, and Sentiment Analysis. \nid_nergrit_ner is the Named Entity Recognition of this dataset collection which contains 18 entities as follow:\n    'CRD': Cardinal\n    'DAT': Date\n    'EVT': Event\n    'FAC': Facility\n    'GPE': Geopolitical Entity\n    'LAW': Law Entity (such as Undang-Undang)\n    'LOC': Location\n    'MON': Money\n    'NOR': Political Organization\n    'ORD': Ordinal\n    'ORG': Organization\n    'PER': Person\n    'PRC': Percent\n    'PRD': Product\n    'QTY': Quantity\n    'REG': Religion\n    'TIM': Time\n    'WOA': Work of Art\n    'LAN': Language\n", "citation": "@inproceedings{id_nergrit_ner,\n  author    = {Gria Inovasi Teknologi},\n  title     = {NERGRIT CORPUS},\n  year      = {2019},\n  url       = {https://github.com/grit-id/nergrit-corpus},\n}\n", "homepage": "https://github.com/grit-id/nergrit-corpus", "license": "", "features": {"id": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "tokens": {"feature": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}, "ner_tags": {"feature": {"num_classes": 39, "names": ["B-CRD", "B-DAT", "B-EVT", "B-FAC", "B-GPE", "B-LAN", "B-LAW", "B-LOC", "B-MON", "B-NOR", "B-ORD", "B-ORG", "B-PER", "B-PRC", "B-PRD", "B-QTY", "B-REG", "B-TIM", "B-WOA", "I-CRD", "I-DAT", "I-EVT", "I-FAC", "I-GPE", "I-LAN", "I-LAW", "I-LOC", "I-MON", "I-NOR", "I-ORD", "I-ORG", "I-PER", "I-PRC", "I-PRD", "I-QTY", "I-REG", "I-TIM", "I-WOA", "O"], "names_file": null, "id": null, "_type": "ClassLabel"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}}, "post_processed": null, "supervised_keys": null, "builder_name": "id_nergrit_ner", "config_name": "id_nergrit_ner", "version": {"version_str": "1.0.0", "description": null, "major": 1, "minor": 0, "patch": 0}, "splits": {"train": {"name": "train", "num_bytes": 5428411, "num_examples": 12532, "dataset_name": "id_nergrit_ner"}, "test": {"name": "test", "num_bytes": 1135577, "num_examples": 2399, "dataset_name": "id_nergrit_ner"}, "validation": {"name": "validation", "num_bytes": 1086437, "num_examples": 2521, "dataset_name": "id_nergrit_ner"}}, "download_checksums": {"https://github.com/cahya-wirawan/indonesian-language-models/raw/master/data/nergrit-corpus_20190726_corrected.tgz": {"num_bytes": 13966780, "checksum": "ef0e5a592631167129f44ff575f63e80fed6e59b63b443b8e7dcea39c1cedd66"}}, "download_size": 13966780, "post_processing_size": null, "dataset_size": 7650425, "size_in_bytes": 21617205}}