{"ronec": {"description": "The RONEC (Named Entity Corpus for the Romanian language) dataset  contains over 26000 entities in ~5000 annotated sentence,\nbelonging to 16 distinct classes. It represents the first initiative in the Romanian language space specifically targeted for named entity recognition\n", "citation": "@article{dumitrescu2019introducing,\n  title={Introducing RONEC--the Romanian Named Entity Corpus},\n  author={Dumitrescu, Stefan Daniel and Avram, Andrei-Marius},\n  journal={arXiv preprint arXiv:1909.01247},\n  year={2019}\n}\n", "homepage": "https://github.com/dumitrescustefan/ronec", "license": "MIT License", "features": {"id": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "tokens": {"feature": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}, "ner_tags": {"feature": {"num_classes": 33, "names": ["O", "B-DATETIME", "B-EVENT", "B-FACILITY", "B-GPE", "B-LANGUAGE", "B-LOC", "B-MONEY", "B-NAT_REL_POL", "B-NUMERIC_VALUE", "B-ORDINAL", "B-ORGANIZATION", "B-PERIOD", "B-PERSON", "B-PRODUCT", "B-QUANTITY", "B-WORK_OF_ART", "I-DATETIME", "I-EVENT", "I-FACILITY", "I-GPE", "I-LANGUAGE", "I-LOC", "I-MONEY", "I-NAT_REL_POL", "I-NUMERIC_VALUE", "I-ORDINAL", "I-ORGANIZATION", "I-PERIOD", "I-PERSON", "I-PRODUCT", "I-QUANTITY", "I-WORK_OF_ART"], "names_file": null, "id": null, "_type": "ClassLabel"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}}, "post_processed": null, "supervised_keys": null, "builder_name": "ronec", "config_name": "ronec", "version": {"version_str": "1.0.0", "description": null, "major": 1, "minor": 0, "patch": 0}, "splits": {"train": {"name": "train", "num_bytes": 2518890, "num_examples": 4173, "dataset_name": "ronec"}, "test": {"name": "test", "num_bytes": 317141, "num_examples": 522, "dataset_name": "ronec"}, "validation": {"name": "validation", "num_bytes": 320904, "num_examples": 522, "dataset_name": "ronec"}}, "download_checksums": {"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dumitrescustefan/ronec/master/ronec/conllup/raw/train.conllu": {"num_bytes": 11583235, "checksum": "686b230c30866afa4b9c4b2b511062c2562e84af4d9c71035a92712cc90aba21"}, "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dumitrescustefan/ronec/master/ronec/conllup/raw/dev.conllu": {"num_bytes": 1478451, "checksum": "b99f1b7d9fef24635ee66b925e039663ef7fbe5c5a7851ffdb3efa0d9395ad41"}, "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dumitrescustefan/ronec/master/ronec/conllup/raw/test.conllu": {"num_bytes": 1464643, "checksum": "7b1f71cfdbd5fc71e44051e1028369f5245afbfd7b17730b31b785bbff3f9c56"}}, "download_size": 14526329, "post_processing_size": null, "dataset_size": 3156935, "size_in_bytes": 17683264}}
