{"germeval_14": {"description": "The GermEval 2014 NER Shared Task builds on a new dataset with German Named Entity annotation with the following properties:    - The data was sampled from German Wikipedia and News Corpora as a collection of citations.    - The dataset covers over 31,000 sentences corresponding to over 590,000 tokens.    - The NER annotation uses the NoSta-D guidelines, which extend the Tübingen Treebank guidelines,      using four main NER categories with sub-structure, and annotating embeddings among NEs      such as [ORG FC Kickers [LOC Darmstadt]].\n", "citation": "@inproceedings{benikova-etal-2014-nosta,\n    title = {NoSta-D Named Entity Annotation for German: Guidelines and Dataset},\n    author = {Benikova, Darina  and\n      Biemann, Chris  and\n      Reznicek, Marc},\n    booktitle = {Proceedings of the Ninth International Conference on Language Resources and Evaluation ({LREC}'14)},\n    month = {may},\n    year = {2014},\n    address = {Reykjavik, Iceland},\n    publisher = {European Language Resources Association (ELRA)},\n    url = {http://www.lrec-conf.org/proceedings/lrec2014/pdf/276_Paper.pdf},\n    pages = {2524--2531},\n}\n", "homepage": "https://sites.google.com/site/germeval2014ner/", "license": "", "features": {"id": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "source": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "tokens": {"feature": {"dtype": "string", "id": null, "_type": "Value"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}, "ner_tags": {"feature": {"num_classes": 25, "names": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOCderiv", "I-LOCderiv", "B-LOCpart", "I-LOCpart", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORGderiv", "I-ORGderiv", "B-ORGpart", "I-ORGpart", "B-OTH", "I-OTH", "B-OTHderiv", "I-OTHderiv", "B-OTHpart", "I-OTHpart", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERderiv", "I-PERderiv", "B-PERpart", "I-PERpart"], "names_file": null, "id": null, "_type": "ClassLabel"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}, "nested_ner_tags": {"feature": {"num_classes": 25, "names": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOCderiv", "I-LOCderiv", "B-LOCpart", "I-LOCpart", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORGderiv", "I-ORGderiv", "B-ORGpart", "I-ORGpart", "B-OTH", "I-OTH", "B-OTHderiv", "I-OTHderiv", "B-OTHpart", "I-OTHpart", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PERderiv", "I-PERderiv", "B-PERpart", "I-PERpart"], "names_file": null, "id": null, "_type": "ClassLabel"}, "length": -1, "id": null, "_type": "Sequence"}}, "post_processed": null, "supervised_keys": null, "builder_name": "germ_eval14", "config_name": "germeval_14", "version": {"version_str": "2.0.0", "description": null, "major": 2, "minor": 0, "patch": 0}, "splits": {"train": {"name": "train", "num_bytes": 13816714, "num_examples": 24000, "dataset_name": "germ_eval14"}, "validation": {"name": "validation", "num_bytes": 1266974, "num_examples": 2200, "dataset_name": "germ_eval14"}, "test": {"name": "test", "num_bytes": 2943201, "num_examples": 5100, "dataset_name": "germ_eval14"}}, "download_checksums": {"https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&id=1Jjhbal535VVz2ap4v4r_rN1UEHTdLK5P": {"num_bytes": 7882358, "checksum": "1e5a803d81f5fe6ade54700a7e8e9107a45edba80469d42e41a360550d1758e7"}, "https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&id=1ZfRcQThdtAR5PPRjIDtrVP7BtXSCUBbm": {"num_bytes": 723876, "checksum": "d69d1347847e3ac0d1bfd14d7e5c0713dcb82899624301ced6df807dbb070056"}, "https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&id=1u9mb7kNJHWQCWyweMDRMuTFoOHOfeBTH": {"num_bytes": 1682738, "checksum": "9405e49532379f3aee048851d116b35823d31c04e9521b87a9c4e6572c269097"}}, "download_size": 10288972, "post_processing_size": null, "dataset_size": 18026889, "size_in_bytes": 28315861}}